<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="79">
    <author>Achimobil, Agro Tonho</author>
    <contributor>Agro Tonho, bgo1973</contributor>
    <version>1.0.0.2</version>
    <title>
        <en>John Deere CS 690 And 606SH/608SH Lavender</en>
        <de>John Deere CS 690 Und 606SH/608SH Lavendel</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
<![CDATA[The John Deere CS690 has served well as a cotton harvester. Due to its capacity and ease of use, its scope of duties was expanded to include lavender. For this purpose, the cutters were modified to cut lavender in a realistic size in 3 or 4 rows.
The pressing chamber has been specially corrected for lavender so that the valuable lavender oil does not leak out on the field during pressing and the pressing ensures that the fresh harvest lasts longer until it can be processed further.

To use this Harvester it is required that Lavender is build in the Map.

This is a conversion of the <a href="https://www.farming-simulator.com/mod.php?mod_id=272153&title=fs2022">cotton harvester by Agro Tonho</a>.
Feel free to post error messages and suggestions for improvement in the <a href="https://github.com/Achimobil/FS22_John_Deere_CS_690_lavender">GitHub</a>.
This makes the pressed bales with a lower capacity than comparable bales with cotton.

CS690 Specifications:
- Price: $613,000
- Power: 550 hp
- Top speed: 19.88 km/h
- Optional transport wheels, double front wheels and tracks, each with two variations of the rear wheels
- Continental, Michelin, Mitas, Trelleborg, Vredestein and BKT tire options
- 4 optional mirrors, 3 of them with 4 mirrors and one optional with 6 mirrors
- Optional numbers from 1 to 9
- Optional camera monitor inside
- Optional 4 shades of cabin glass
- Realistic animations on interior panels
- Door opening animation influencing the interior sound, making the animation more realistic
- Bench adjustment animations affecting the internal camera position
- Animation of the sunshade, mirrors and steering column
- Animation of the driver when turning on the key

Characteristics of headers:
Both have optional weights
Working speed: 6.2 mph

John Deere 606SH:
- Price: $37000
- Working width: 4.88 meters

John Deere 608SH:
- Price: $50000
- Working width: 6.8 meters]]>
        </en>
        <de>
<![CDATA[Der John Deere CS690 hat als Baumwollernter gute Dienste geleistet. Aufgrund seiner Kapazität und guten Bedienbarkeit wurde sein Aufgabenfeld auf Lavendel erweitert. Hierzu wurden die Schneidwerke umgebaut um Lavendel in realistischer Größe in 3 bzw 4 reihen zu schneiden.
Die Presskammer wurde speziell für Lavendel korrigiert, damit das Wertvolle Lavendelöl nicht schon beim Pressen auf dem Feld austritt und durch die Pressung wird eine Längere Haltbarkeit der frischen Ernte erreicht, bis diese weiter verarbeitet werden kann.
Hierdurch sind die gepressten Ballen mit einer geringeren Kapazität als vergleichbare Ballen mit Baumwolle.

Um diese Erntemaschine zu benutzen, muss Lavendel auf der Karte eingebaut sein.

Dieser ist ein Umbau des <a href="https://www.farming-simulator.com/mod.php?mod_id=272153&title=fs2022">Baumwollernters von Agro Tonho</a>.
Fehlermeldungen und Verbesserungsvorschläge gern im <a href="https://github.com/Achimobil/FS22_John_Deere_CS_690_lavender">GitHub</a> anbringen.

CS690-Spezifikationen:
- Preis: 613.000 €
- Leistung: 550 PS
- Höchstgeschwindigkeit: 32 km/h
- Optionale Transporträder, doppelte Vorderräder und Ketten, jeweils mit zwei Varianten der Hinterräder
- Reifenoptionen von Continental, Michelin, Mitas, Trelleborg, Vredestein und BKT
- 4 optionale Spiegel, 3 davon mit 4 Spiegeln und einer optional mit 6 Spiegeln
- Optionale Zahlen von 1 bis 9
- Optionaler Kameramonitor im Inneren
- Optional 4 Farbtöne Kabinenscheiben
- Realistische Animationen auf Innenverkleidungen
- Türöffnungsanimation, die den Innenraumklang beeinflusst und die Animation realistischer macht
- Animationen zur Bankeinstellung, die sich auf die interne Kameraposition auswirken
- Animation von Sonnenschutz, Spiegeln und Lenksäule
- Animation des Fahrers beim Einschalten des Schlüssels

Eigenschaften Schneidwerke:
Beide haben optionale Gewichte
Arbeitsgeschwindigkeit: 10 km/h

John Deere 606SH:
- Preis: 37000 €
- Arbeitsbreite: 4,88 Meter

John Deere 608SH:
- Preis: 50000 €
- Arbeitsbreite: 6,8 Meter]]>
        </de>
        <br>
<![CDATA[O John Deere CS690 serviu bem como colheitadeira de algodão. Pela sua capacidade e facilidade de uso, seu escopo de atribuições foi ampliado para incluir a alfazema. Para tanto, os cortadores foram modificados para cortar a alfazema em tamanho realista em 3 ou 4 fileiras.
A câmara de prensagem foi especialmente corrigida para lavanda, para que o valioso óleo de lavanda não vaze no campo durante a prensagem e a prensagem garante que a colheita fresca dure mais tempo até que possa ser processada posteriormente.

Para usar esse Harvester, é necessário que Lavender esteja construído no mapa.

Esta é uma conversão da <a href="https://www.farming-simulator.com/mod.php?mod_id=272153&title=fs2022">colhedora de algodão da Agro Tonho</a>.
Sinta-se à vontade para postar mensagens de erro e sugestões de melhorias no <a href="https://github.com/Achimobil/FS22_John_Deere_CS_690_lavender">GitHub</a>.

Especificações CS690
- Preço: 613000€
- Potência: 550 CVs
- Velocidade máxima: 32 km/h
- Opcionais de rodas para transporte, duplas frontais e esteiras, cada uma com duas variações das rodas traseiras
- Opcionais de pneus Continental, Michelin, Mitas, Trelleborg, Vredestein e BKT
- 4 opcionais de espelhos, sendo 3 deles com 4 espelhos e um opcional com 6 espelhos
- Opcionais de números do 1 até o 9
- Opcional do monitor da câmera no interior
- Opcional de 4 tonalidades dos vidros da cabine
- Animações realistas nos painéis do interior
- Animação de abertura da porta influenciando no som do interior, tornando a animação mais realista
- Animações de regulagem do banco afetando na posição da câmera interna
- Animação do para sol, espelhos e coluna do volante
- Animação do motorista ao ligar a chave

Características dos cabeçalhos
Ambos possuem opcionais de pesos
Velocidade de trabalho: 10 km/h

John Deere 606SH
- Preço: 37000€
- Largura de trabalho: 4,88 metros

John Deere 608SH
- Preço: 50000€
- Largura de trabalho: 6,8 metros]]>
        </br>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_CS690.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />
    <storeItems>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="CS690.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="606SH.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="608SH.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
	<bales>
		<bale filename="bales/lavenderRoundbale238.xml" />
	</bales>
	<fillTypes filename="fillTypes.xml"/>
	
	<vehicleTypes>
		<type name="CS690" parent="combineDrivable" className="Vehicle" filename="$dataS/scripts/vehicles/Vehicle.lua">
            <specialization name="baler" />
        </type>				
	</vehicleTypes>
	
	<l10n>
		<text name="pesos"><en>Weights</en><de>Gewichte</de><br>Pesos</br></text>
		<text name="numeros"><en>Numbers</en><de>Zahlen</de><br>Números</br></text>
		<text name="transporte"><en>Transport</en><de>Transport</de><br>Transporte</br></text>
		<text name="espelhos"><en>Mirrors</en><de>Spiegel</de><br>espelhos</br></text>
		<text name="triplo"><en>Triple mirrors</en><de>Dreifachspiegel</de><br>Espelhos triplos</br></text>
		<text name="duploverde"><en>Double mirrors with green support</en><de>Doppelspiegel mit grüner Halterung</de><br>Espelhos duplos com suporte verde</br></text>
		<text name="duplopreto"><en>Double mirrors with black support</en><de>Doppelspiegel mit schwarzem Träger</de><br>Espelhos duplos com suporte preto</br></text>
		<text name="janelas"><en>Windows</en><de>Fenster</de><br>Janelas</br></text>
		<text name="fume1"><en>Smoked 1</en><de>Getönt 1</de><br>Fumê 1</br></text>
		<text name="fume2"><en>Smoked 2</en><de>Getönt 2</de><br>Fumê 2</br></text>
		<text name="fume3"><en>Smoked 3</en><de>Getönt 3</de><br>Fumê 3</br></text>
		<text name="monitorcamera"><en>Camera panel</en><de>Kamerapanel</de><br>Painel da câmera</br></text>
		<text name="geral"><en>General</en><de>allgemein</de><br>Geral</br></text>
		<text name="cs690Lavender"><en>CS690 Lavender</en><de>CS690 Lavendel</de><br>CS690 Lavanda</br></text>
		<text name="608shLavender"><en>608SH Lavender</en><de>608SH Lavendel</de><br>608SH Lavanda</br></text>
		<text name="606shLavender"><en>606SH Lavender</en><de>606SH Lavendel</de><br>606SH Lavanda</br></text>
		<text name="fillType_roundBaleLavender"><en>Lavender Bale</en><de>Lavendel Ballen</de><br>Lavanda Fardo</br></text>
	</l10n>
</modDesc>
