<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="no" ?>
<modDesc descVersion="75">
    <author>Agro Tonho</author>
    <version>1.0.0.0</version>
    <title>
        <en>John Deere CS 690 And 606SH/608SH</en>
        <de>John Deere CS 690 Und 606SH/608SH</de>
    </title>
    <description>
        <en>
<![CDATA[The John Deere CS690 cotton picker is here to enhance your property. With its non-stop bale production capacity, your farm's yield only tends to grow, as well as its two header options scale the job according to the size and needs of your property.
In this mod you will find a cotton picker John Deere CS690 and two hitchable headers John Deere 606SH and 608 SH

CS690 Specifications:
- Price: $613,000
- Power: 550 hp
- Top speed: 19.88 km/h
- Optional transport wheels, double front wheels and tracks, each with two variations of the rear wheels
- Continental, Michelin, Mitas, Trelleborg, Vredestein and BKT tire options
- 4 optional mirrors, 3 of them with 4 mirrors and one optional with 6 mirrors
- Optional numbers from 1 to 9
- Optional camera monitor inside
- Optional 4 shades of cabin glass
- Realistic animations on interior panels
- Door opening animation influencing the interior sound, making the animation more realistic
- Bench adjustment animations affecting the internal camera position
- Animation of the sunshade, mirrors and steering column
- Animation of the driver when turning on the key

Characteristics of headers:
Both have optional weights
Working speed: 6.2 mph

John Deere 606SH:
- Price: $37000
- Working width: 4.88 meters

John Deere 608SH:
- Price: $50000
- Working width: 6.8 meters]]>
        </en>
        <de>
<![CDATA[Der John Deere CS690 Baumwollernter ist dazu da, um Ihren Betrieb zu verbessern. Mit seiner Non-Stop-Ballenproduktionskapazität wird der Ertrag Ihres Betriebes immer größer, und seine zwei Schneidwerkoptionen passen die Arbeit an die Größe und die Bedürfnisse Ihres Betriebs an.
In diesem Mod finden Sie einen John Deere CS690 Baumwollernter und zwei anbaubare Schneidwerke John Deere 606SH und 608 SH.

CS690-Spezifikationen:
- Preis: 613.000 €
- Leistung: 550 PS
- Höchstgeschwindigkeit: 32 km/h
- Optionale Transporträder, doppelte Vorderräder und Ketten, jeweils mit zwei Varianten der Hinterräder
- Reifenoptionen von Continental, Michelin, Mitas, Trelleborg, Vredestein und BKT
- 4 optionale Spiegel, 3 davon mit 4 Spiegeln und einer optional mit 6 Spiegeln
- Optionale Zahlen von 1 bis 9
- Optionaler Kameramonitor im Inneren
- Optional 4 Farbtöne Kabinenscheiben
- Realistische Animationen auf Innenverkleidungen
- Türöffnungsanimation, die den Innenraumklang beeinflusst und die Animation realistischer macht
- Animationen zur Bankeinstellung, die sich auf die interne Kameraposition auswirken
- Animation von Sonnenschutz, Spiegeln und Lenksäule
- Animation des Fahrers beim Einschalten des Schlüssels

Eigenschaften Schneidwerke:
Beide haben optionale Gewichte
Arbeitsgeschwindigkeit: 10 km/h

John Deere 606SH:
- Preis: 37000 €
- Arbeitsbreite: 4,88 Meter

John Deere 608SH:
- Preis: 50000 €
- Arbeitsbreite: 6,8 Meter]]>
        </de>
        <br>
<![CDATA[A selecionadora de algodão John Deere CS690 veio para incrementar a sua propriedade. Com a capacidade de produção de fardos sem parar, o rendimento de sua fazenda só tende a crescer, assim como suas duas opções de cabeçalho dimensionam o trabalho de acordo com o tamanho e necessidade da sua propriedade.
Neste mod você encontra uma selecionadora de algodão John Deere CS690 e dois cabeçalhos engatáveis John Deere 606SH e 608 SH
Especificações CS690
- Preço: 613000€
- Potência: 550 CVs
- Velocidade máxima: 32 km/h
- Opcionais de rodas para transporte, duplas frontais e esteiras, cada uma com duas variações das rodas traseiras
- Opcionais de pneus Continental, Michelin, Mitas, Trelleborg, Vredestein e BKT
- 4 opcionais de espelhos, sendo 3 deles com 4 espelhos e um opcional com 6 espelhos
- Opcionais de números do 1 até o 9
- Opcional do monitor da câmera no interior
- Opcional de 4 tonalidades dos vidros da cabine
- Animações realistas nos painéis do interior
- Animação de abertura da porta influenciando no som do interior, tornando a animação mais realista
- Animações de regulagem do banco afetando na posição da câmera interna
- Animação do para sol, espelhos e coluna do volante
- Animação do motorista ao ligar a chave

Características dos cabeçalhos
Ambos possuem opcionais de pesos
Velocidade de trabalho: 10 km/h

John Deere 606SH
- Preço: 37000€
- Largura de trabalho: 4,88 metros

John Deere 608SH
- Preço: 50000€
- Largura de trabalho: 6,8 metros]]>
        </br>
    </description>
    <iconFilename>icon_CS690.dds</iconFilename>
    <multiplayer supported="true" />
    <storeItems>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="CS690.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="606SH.xml"/>
		<storeItem xmlFilename="608SH.xml"/>
    </storeItems>
	
	<vehicleTypes>
		<type name="CS690" parent="combineDrivable" className="Vehicle" filename="$dataS/scripts/vehicles/Vehicle.lua">
            <specialization name="baler" />
        </type>				
	</vehicleTypes>
	
	<l10n>
		<text name="pesos"><en>Weights</en><de>Gewichte</de><br>Pesos</br></text>
		<text name="numeros"><en>Numbers</en><de>Zahlen</de><br>Números</br></text>
		<text name="transporte"><en>Transport</en><de>Transport</de><br>Transporte</br></text>
		<text name="espelhos"><en>Mirrors</en><de>Spiegel</de><br>espelhos</br></text>
		<text name="triplo"><en>Triple mirrors</en><de>Dreifachspiegel</de><br>Espelhos triplos</br></text>
		<text name="duploverde"><en>Double mirrors with green support</en><de>Doppelspiegel mit grüner Halterung</de><br>Espelhos duplos com suporte verde</br></text>
		<text name="duplopreto"><en>Double mirrors with black support</en><de>Doppelspiegel mit schwarzem Träger</de><br>Espelhos duplos com suporte preto</br></text>
		<text name="janelas"><en>Windows</en><de>Fenster</de><br>Janelas</br></text>
		<text name="fume1"><en>Smoked 1</en><de>Getönt 1</de><br>Fumê 1</br></text>
		<text name="fume2"><en>Smoked 2</en><de>Getönt 2</de><br>Fumê 2</br></text>
		<text name="fume3"><en>Smoked 3</en><de>Getönt 3</de><br>Fumê 3</br></text>
		<text name="monitorcamera"><en>Camera panel</en><de>Kamerapanel</de><br>Painel da câmera</br></text>
	</l10n>
</modDesc>
